A Ferell woman?
Yes, Sir. There's a Ferell woman in GU.
Are you sure?
As far as I know,
Garpidio doesn't have a granddaughter.
Well, those boys claim that she's a Ferell.
Can we talk?
I want to check on you and Camille.
She got suspended.
That's why the last time I heard,
her father was fuming mad.
What is this, Aira?
Is this a trap?
Did you make me come here
so she can laugh at me?
This is us showing you
that we understand
what you're going through now.
We want to assure you
that whatever you're going through,
we are here for you.
And if you need help,
we're ready to help you, whatever that is.
Still alive, Don Rogelio?
I should ask you that question.
Bad weeds take a long time to die.
So, what's with this call?
Is the world ending?
No, not yet.
But one of my men, George,
had an unfortunate encounter
with your grandchildren.
I think that's your superpower, Florence.
Everybody eventually wants
to be friends with you.
Even Antonia, who is the former ex
of your boyfriend, Nero.
I want to change my life.
I don't want to say bad things
about others...
but...
Florence deserves to know.
It's not
that I want to badmouth others but...
be careful of Antonia.
Why?
Well, she's the real deal, Florence.
I mean, I admit that I'm not a good girl...
but Antonia seems like
she's hiding a different persona...
and that's scarier.
Excuse me, Don Ferell,
Florence is here already.
Grandfather Garp?
So you're Florence Dela Cruz?
Florence,
I'd like you to meet George Villarico.
He's an associate of Don Rogelio Almero
and this dashing gentleman here...
I am Rogelio Almero.
This guy, George,
claims that you attacked him.
Is it true?
Yes, Grandfather Garp, that's true.
So it's true.
I kicked him on his...
Beep... Beep, beep...
First, why did you meddle?
He was talking with his daughter.
And then when he asked you
to leave him alone,
you kicked him there.
Very disrespectful, Florence.
I cannot tolerate such behavior... Cannot be.
I'm sorry if... I kicked you on the... beep.
But Grandfather Garp,
if I need to do it again, I'll do it.
What? You'll do it again?
Why?
Because he was physically
hurting his daughter.
What reached you was fake news,
that I just hurt him without a valid reason.
I was defending Camille,
and that's what my mother and father
taught me, Grandfather Garp.
If I see someone getting abused, I must help.
George, is this true?
Pardon me for what I did, Sir.
Please let me explain.
I'm under a lot of pressure
and when I found out
that Camille has a problem in school,
I completely lost my temper.
Let's talk later.
What you did is admirable, Miss.
I commend your courage
for standing up for others.
So we've settled everything then, Almero.
And...
the both of you don't have
any more business here?
So I suggest you just go.
I think I also owe Garpidio an apology.
I'm sorry to have wasted your time.
Florence...
Is it true
that you kicked him there directly?
Yes.
Beep.
Good girl.
You humiliated me in front of Garpidio.
But, Sir, she meddled with
my conversation with Camille.
You've hurt your own daughter!
We are given children to love,
to take care of, protect, and not hurt them.
If you lay your hands on your daughter again,
I'm going to destroy you.
Now, get out of my face.
Dad?
Son... remember I told you
that I saw this girl
who could possibly be your missing daughter?
Yes, what about it?
I saw her again and up close this time.
And I could feel that she's Celestina,
my missing granddaughter.
Son... I think I found your daughter.
I found Celestina.
What?
Let's go.
You guys think Florence will be okay?
Grandfather Garp looked kind of mad
when he found out what happened earlier.
This is your fault, Troy.
You dropped grandfather's name.
That was my way to avoid further violence.
And how would I know
that Mr. Villarico is a staff of Don Rogelio?
And why are you all pointing the blame at me?
All of you played along too.
What's up, boys?
Nothing, Grandfather.
We're just discussing the Grand GU Ball.
- Yes, Grandfather.
- This year will be different.
Yes, Grandfather,
it's going to be attractive.
Do you believe them?
No.
Because when we arrived,
they became suddenly quiet and nervous.
Marites said
that whenever they are talking about you,
they'll suddenly become quiet
once you arrive.
Who is Marites?
Marites is the term for gossip-mongers.
It came from "Mare, anong latest"?
And then it evolved to "Mare, latest"?
And now, it's Marites.
Oh. Well, people nowadays.
At least it settles that.
How about your issue
with Don Rogelio, Grandfather?
Rogelio and I is a...
Our relationship is what you call...
You kids call nowadays...
"frenemies".
Why don't you guys solve your squabbles,
Grandfather?
You're already old
and you guys are still competing
with your business ventures.
That's right, Grandfather.
The status of your relationship
seems complicated,
but you still have collaboration projects,
right?
The on-and-off battle between me and Rogelio
goes a long way back,
and it's not just about politics.
Don't tell me, Grandfather,
you even had a competition about love?
Yes.
Rogelio and I are best friends.
I was even the bridge
when he was courting your grandmother.
But your grandmother and I became closer.
To make the story short, we became a couple.
You're our idol, Grandfather.
You're really something else,
Grandfather Garp.
This is the first time we learned
that Don Rogelio liked Grandmother.
And that's how we became frenemies.
To be honest,
before Rogelio even set eyes
on your grandmother,
I've already fallen in love with her.
But Rogelio and I were best of friends,
so I stepped aside.
But what can I do,
your grandmother really loves me.
That's right. Of course,
that's Grandfather Garp...
Charming, kind, and sweet.
Of course, she'll choose you.
Deserve!
Unfortunately, my friendship with Rogelio
was ruined.
From then on, he resented me.
We continued our partnership
in our businesses but...
things have never been the same.
All your grandmother's efforts
for Rogelio and I to patch things up
didn't work, because we always fight.
And that affected our business decisions.
We lost so many transactions
because we can't get along,
even with the smallest details,
until our partnership got dissolved.
To be honest, I miss my best friend.
Rogelio and I are like brothers.
Not that I'm blaming Amanda,
but I hope from the start,
we were able to talk about it.
Because now...
Rogelio feels that I betrayed him
because I didn't tell him right away
that I have feelings for Amanda too.
Guys, help me.
I'm chatting with this chick.
You know, I'm not used to chatting.
I'm a skilled face-to-face talker.
What's the difference between chatting online
and chatting in person?
That's right.
In case you forget, Aldus,
Troy has a typographical error problem.
Remember when he was texting his crush,
instead of texting,
"I want to tuck you up in bed",
he texted "I want to F you up in bed".
What's with you?
- That was good.
- What will I tell her?
Basic... Ask first what she looks like.
Or better, ask her to send her picture.
There.
Baby girl, send me your picture.
Baby girl?
So, beauty is just your qualifications
to talk to someone?
You'd lose interest
if you are talking to an ugly person.
- Exactly.
- What?
Wouldn't you lose your interest more
if you're talking to someone who's...
whom Taylor Swift would be ashamed of,
but you'll also be embarrassed
with the five-year-old capacity of her brain?
And what if she gets turned off
because you asked her
to send a picture so soon,
and it just so happened that she's beautiful
like a goddess, intelligent, honor student?
You'll quickly lose the chance
to have a potential beauty-and-brains friend,
or even a girlfriend.
Florence has a point.
Okay, since you all know too much,
why don't you do this, since you're good?
- Do the honors.
- Stay here.
Move.
Hold this.
Let's see what you can do.
[alvis_jester: What's your favorite novel?]
[ninjacopygirl1409: Little Lord Fauntleroy.
My teacher asked me to read it before,]
[and I fell in love with the main character.]
This girl will like you.
She is fond of boys who are mama's boy.
Just like Cedric Errol,
the main character in her favorite novel.
Just like you, a mama's boy.
Mama's boy? Of course not.
No? What do you mean you're not?
I hear you every day calling your mom.
"Good night, Mama."
"Good morning, Mama."
"I love you, Mama."
- "I miss you."
- That's so sweet.
So you're a mama's boy in a positive light.
See? You suddenly became meek.
What's wrong with loving your mom?
No, don't be ashamed of being a mama's boy.
[alvis_jester: How many siblings
do you have?]
[ninjacopygirl1409: Three,
and I'm the only girl and the youngest.]
[alvis_jester: Are you a K-Pop fan?]
[ninjacopygirl1409: I'm more
of a PPop fan, SB19, FTW,]
[but I also love BTS and EXO.]
Deal-breaker.
[alvis_jester: Do you like basketball?]
[ninjacopygirl1409:
I got influenced by my brothers.]
[I love Draymond Green.]
I like this girl.
This girl is mine, dude.
But...
Florence, wait.
Why does it seem
like you're doing an interview?
Aren't you going to say some things about me?
About you?
Interview?
This is not like an interview.
That's the problem with you.
You're always after yourselves.
And you want to impress,
that's why you end up
talking about yourselves.
"I'm handsome", "This is what I want",
"I'm playing basketball", blah blah...
So the people you're talking to
have lost their interest in you.
If you want the girl,
you have to make them feel
that you're interested in her.
What's there not to like?
[ninjacopygirl1409:
How about you, alvis_jester?]
[Tell me something about you too.
What's your favorite novel?]
There's your cue.
Now is the time you chat about yourself,
and not at the beginning
when you are just starting.
It's game time.
It's crunch time, boys.
Look. We're both gamers.
- Yes, sir.
- What are you waiting for?
Ask her to send a picture.
A picture.
- Picture.
- No, bro.
I don't want to pressure her.
She might get turned off by me.
Good job, Troy.
Fast learner, in fairness.
But, Troy, just in case you don't like
her physical appearance,
don't just dump her.
That's rude.
- Yeah.
- Of course not.
And I like this girl.
I want her to be my friend.
And beauty is not a qualification
to become my friend.
Look at yourself.
We're friends, right?
Are you telling me that I'm not beautiful?
Then why do I see a queen beauty
whenever I see my reflection?
You're so beautiful. You're so charming.
Why don't you ask... Nero?
Where is he?
Where is that fool?
[Henry's Roasted Chicken]
Okay, let's see each other in school,
and let's do a checklist
so we can make sure
we won't forget anything for the ball.
Okay, bye.
Perfect timing, it's freshly cooked.
- Mr. Henry?
- Yes?
I'll have the usual,
not too big but not too small.
I'll have the medium size,
it shouldn't be too big.
That's it.
And don't forget my favorite sauce.
There, the other one, Mister.
- Florence?
- That's it.
Don Rogelio, it's you.
Good morning.
Look, Florence, I'm sorry
that we met under unfortunate circumstances.
But when I learned that there was an incident
involving the grandsons of Don Garpidio
with one of my people,
I had to deal with it right away.
Garpidio and I have had a colorful history,
that's why I need to fix it right away
before things get worse.
I understand, there's nothing to worry about.
But now that I know the truth,
I have dealt with George,
and I assure you
that he will no longer hurt Camille.
That's great to hear.
Oh, but look, what do we have here?
Is Mr. Henry's chicken your favorite too?
Yes, this is my favorite chicken
in the whole Levante.
When I'm sad, that's my comfort food.
That makes me happy.
Just a little push
and I'll call it
the joyful chicken of Mr. Henry.
Is this your favorite too?
Of course.
Did you know
that Mr. Henry uses mango tree wood
for roasting?
That's why his chicken is delicious.
Wow, that's cool.
You also know a lot about food.
Actually, I didn't discover this place.
It was my daughter-in-law...
Alyanna.
Unfortunately, she's no longer here.
That's why I pass by here to remember her.
How wonderful a woman she was.
That's sad.
But it's okay. Don't worry, because...
Can you smell that?
- Can you smell that?
- Yes.
It smells like
freshly cooked roasted chicken of Mr. Henry.
The scent is powerful, right?
You can smell it right away.
That's why I'm sure
Ms. Alyanna can smell that in heaven.
And I'm sure
she's looking at St. Peter's chicken
with dagger looks
because she wants to roast it.
You are adorable, Florence.
It's been a while
since someone made me laugh.
I hope this is not the last time
I'll be talking to you.
That's for sure,
especially now that we get along
when it comes to roasted chicken.
Of course.
Roasted chicken buddies.
Chicken buddies for life.
- Let's order now.
- It's done.
- Thank you.
- I'll pay for this.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, add some more.
Okay, how many?
Three more.
- Coming right up.
- Three?
- You'll consume all that?
- No, you'll bring that home.
Me?
- I'll bring it home?
- Yes.
I think that's good for a month.
It was suggested to me by my friend
who owns an IT company.
He sent me a computer graphics expert.
I didn't believe it
when the computer graphics specialist told me
that they can give
an approximate image of Celestina
if she grows up into a young woman,
by uploading her baby picture.
Look.
That is the rendered picture.
That is Celestina's baby picture.
I have a strong feeling
that this is
your missing daughter, Celestina.
I believe that this girl is my granddaughter.
You had this kid followed?
Have you gone crazy?
Are you trying to pick a fight
with the Ferells?
What are you talking about?
Can you just stop using my daughter
so you won't feel guilty about what happened?
Do you know what this means?
If people find out about
your obsession with my dead daughter,
they'll think you're crazy.
Celestina is alive!
I can feel it in my heart.
And if you refuse to believe that,
let me look for her.
Don't force yourself to believe
that Celestina is still alive,
because she's already dead.
She and Alyanna are already dead,
and that's what I can feel.
Do you think the hurt I feel
from what happened, has gone?
Do you think I don't wake up every day
feeling sorry because I failed to save them?
There's no minute or moment
that I don't think about them.
But even if it hurts, that's the truth.
I choose to live for them.
That is my way of honoring their memory.
To live.
And somehow try to be happy.
Stop chasing ghosts.
Stop chasing the past
before you get hurt or hurt someone else.
Good morning, Gyronellans.
And we just finished the final plans
for this year's Grand GU Ball.
Confirmed, for the first time ever
in the university's history,
this year's ball will be about giving back.
A charity event with the theme,
"Return to Kindness".
We'll still have the usual fun.
But this time, with a cause.
And each plate will cost about 50,000 pesos,
and all funds raised will be given to
several chosen charitable institutions.
And this is our little way
of reminding people
that we cannot just live
in our own bubble of privilege.
Thank you to
the College of Communication Arts
for this marvelous proposal.
And a special shout out
to its representative,
Ms. Florence Dela Cruz.
You're something else, Florence.
Your mind is not just rich,
but your heart is full too.
Facts.
Anyways, I still have a lot of ideas
within the ball to raise funds.
That's good, Camille, just make suggestions,
but I'll ask a favor from you,
if that's okay.
Anything.
Would it be okay if you oversee some things
during the ball?
I can handle the preparations.
You're not coming?
But why?
Aren't you updated with the latest?
You're always updated.
I'm just a scholar here in the GU.
I can't afford
that 50,000 pesos per plate price.
Gosh.
Oh, yeah, you're poor.
Hey.
- Oh my God. I'm sorry.
- Oh my God.
I didn't mean to offend you.
I just lack sleep.
That's okay, but why did you lack sleep?
Actually, even if you don't lack sleep,
that's the truth.
I'm poor.
I belong to the lower class.
So, Camille,
you take charge during the ball, okay?
Florence, oh, come on.
You'll be there.
And I'm sure Nero will ask you
to be his date.
He'll pay for you.
- That's true.
- Right?
- Oh my, exciting.
- That's exciting.
How about you? Do you have a date already?
Well, this university does not forget easily.
You know what?
Aira and I have already made a mark
as being mean and bullies.
And after what happened on Agora Day,
we no longer expect
that someone will ask us out.
Yeah.
We'll be each other's date.
Yes!
How about you, Lina? You're smiling there.
Do you have a date already?
None.
Should I expect someone to ask me out
when nobody is interested to talk me?
- But I will still attend the ball.
- Seriously?
With a date or none.
No one wants to talk to you?
No one is really interested in you?
- But you lack sleep?
You said you lack sleep last night.
- What did you do?
- Since when did you learn to stay up late?
Hey, Lina is keeping secrets.
You know... I wish someone will ask me out.
- Me too.
Someone will ask you out too.
Of course, you of all people.
OMG!
- What?
- Someone is coming.
Oh my God.
Hi, Camille.
Hi.
Can I invite Chelle to be my date
at the Grand GU Ball?
It's... What?
- Yes, it's Chelle.
- Why are you asking permission from me?
That's because...
Let me stop you there.
I'm a changed person now.
I'm no longer the old Camille.
There's no more leader in our group.
We're all equal.
So... if you want to ask Chelle...
- Chelle...
Go ask her.
Chelle...
Antonia.
Thank you.
You're so sweet, thank you.
- Did you like it?
- Yes, thank you.
Let's go.
- Florence, wait.
- Florence?
Florence, wait.
Please, just let me be alone.
Florence...
Trust me.
The last thing you want
is to be alone at this moment.
We're here for you.
Don't carry this by yourself.
I just want to be alone.
Please let me be.
Florence...
What happened?
Won't you say anything?
You're a philosopher, right?
No, not this time.
I need your soothing words right now.
Your words can lighten my load.
Words, if it comes from the heart,
can be comforting.
But in our case right now... it won't work.
Because it's more effective
if you cry out all your pain.
I once read that God created us
to become the strongest.
Because he gave us the strongest weapon
to protect us from pain.
And that's our ability to cry.
So just cry it all out
and take out all the pain
you're feeling right now.
To be fair,
you were able to say words
that made me feel better.
It's going to be okay.
This is nice.
You remembered well
what's my favorite flower.
Are you happy?
Yes.
That's what's important.
That you're happy.
I'm happy that you invited me, Sir.
Your sizeable contribution
to our beloved university
will certainly be a big help.
I've always been interested
in how I could help Gyronella.
After all, this is one of the best
universities that produce top talents.
And all these years,
my company benefited
from the quality of your graduates.
Thank you, Sir,
for recognizing our hard work.
Indeed, our graduates are
our greatest reputation, our pride.
But if there's one reputation
that we want to erase,
that's our reputation
as a rich kid university.
And with your donation,
we can expand our scholarship program
to make the university accessible
to children from underserved communities.
That's very noble of you, Dean.
It's about time.
It would be a shame if the quality
of education provided by the school
is only exclusive to the wealthy.
Which brings me to my point.
I'm interested in one of your scholars.
Scholars?
Yes.
Her name is Florence Dela Cruz.
And if possible,
I would like to know everything about her.
Is everything okay?
Yes, Grandfather.
Everything is okay.
It's so quiet.
Troy, don't you have any jokes?
I'm still collecting some jokes.
Is it just me
or Florence's cooking is a bit salty?
Yes, it's salty.
Does Florence have a problem?
No one wants to talk.
Okay.
Just be sure...
that if you mess up something, you fix it.
You do what a Ferell should do.
Nero?
Nero!
Are you having fun?
What's your problem?
Not good, Bro.
You're disappointing, man.
You're disappointing.
Please, don't meddle.
What are you talking about?
You're scum, bro!
I told you not to hurt her, but what?
You embarrassed her in front of everyone!
She's important to all of us,
and at the very least,
she has done nothing but become nice to us!
We bullied her from the start,
but what you did is different.
Give us one good reason why you did that.
Because if you can't,
I am ashamed of you as a Ferell.
Relax...
It's your fault.
Why did you do that?
We were clear from the start...
that we were just pretending.
And now that
Antonia and I have gotten back together,
I don't need her anymore.
You're worthless, bro.
You're freaking worthless.
You're annoying, bro.
Babycakes...
You know,
Florence's cooking was a bit salty earlier.
It seems like it lacks the sweetness...
of your love.
You're something else.
You might end up having diabetes
because of too much love from me.
My goodness!
Type 1...
Type 2 Diabetes...
I don't care.
Because what's important is, you're my type.
Stop it.
- Baby, you're something else.
- Ouch, that hurts.
Don Ferell.
It's you... again.
Is there anything we can do for you, Sir?
I want to know what's happening
in this house.
We love each other, Don Ferell.
Sir, I know
that workplace romances are frowned upon
but I hope you'll understand
that we can't control our feelings.
I'm not interested about the two of you.
I've known about that for a long time now.
Really?
What do you want to know?
Clearly, something is going on
between Florence and my grandsons.
I want to find out.
I want to know what's happening.
Well, I agree with you, Sir,
because I've noticed
something new happening to the kids.
But there's only one way to find out,
because the truth will set you free.
Grandfather? What's this for?
This is your chance to tell the truth,
or else,
you know we know
where you feel ticklish the most.
Nero is just using Florence
to get to Antonia.
That's too painful.
So you can imagine how Florence feels.
I'm okay, but of course, I'm a bit...
annoyed with what happened.
But what can I do?
I'm just a plain Dela Cruz, right?
And the reason why I entered GU
is to study and achieve my dreams.
What's your plan?
I'm the only one who truly loves you, Nero.
I'm the only person who can understand you.
I will always protect you,
and I will never break your heart.
What are you talking about?
Break up with her.
Do you think I want to reconcile with you?
Do you think that you have a choice, Nero?
I will make sure...
that Florence will not just
be kicked out of university.
Florence is an easy target.
And I can hurt her in ways
that you can't even imagine.
Nero is not here.
Where did that kid go?